(Josh:)I've always dreamed of having
a brother to play catch with.
(Bernadette:)Keep dreaming.
(Howard:)Hey, I threw out the first pitch
(Howard:)at an Angels game.
Wow.
(Bernadette:)He did it with a robot.
(Josh:)You had sex with a robot?
(Howard:)That's not what she meant.
(Raj:)But technically, yes.
(Leonard:)Hang on, if you're making
all this money,
(Leonard:)where is it?
(Penny:)In a safe place.
(Leonard:)What does that mean,
under your bed?
(Penny:)No, it means
(Penny:)a diversified portfolio
of stocks and bonds.
(Penny:)I'm not overly conservative.
(Penny:)I'm young, so my guy said I
can afford to take some risks.
Wait a minute, you have "a guy"?
(Penny:)Don't you have a guy?
(Leonard:)Why would I have a guy?
I don't have any money!
(Penny:)Oh, sweetie,
(Penny:)you should really
get some money.
(Wil:)For those of you listening
at home,
(Wil:)how great is this?
(Leonard:)Wil, I'm begging you,
just please turn that off.
(Leonard:)Sure.